What's up, y'all?
I just came on while I'm steaming my costume
to remind you that I will be doing a read-through
of What Would the Ancestors Say tonight at 6 p.m. Eastern.
And the link is in the bio, so it's for free.
The link is in the bio, so you can watch it.
And be a part of this process as I continue to develop this show.
We have now been, I say we like it's not a one-woman show.
I have now been doing the show for a year, right?
So it feels very monumental to be at this phase.
And it also has allowed me to learn how I want to develop shows moving forward, right?
That I want to spend the time just improv-ing and playing around
before I sit down and put it to the page.
And that's how I'm going to do my one-woman shows moving forward.
I think my next one-woman show is going to be about Grenada, if you're curious.
So looking forward to seeing that.
So you can, like I said, the link is in the bio.
Hold on one second.
Let me put that here.
Another link in bio for tonight's...
I'm not sure if it's bots, but like when I posted about DC and the occupation coming
to DC, there were like all these bots that were just like, you know, you're fear-mongering.
Like, why would you post this?
Da-da-da-da-da.
And that's exactly...
Mind you, honey, the fact that we're failing to acknowledge that it is an occupation.
So, oh, I have to tell Tonya that.
That's at CIA.
It must be, right?
Because I'm just like, y'all really are not in here trying to tell me that what's coming
to Chicago is not coming to Chicago.
It's in Chicago.
So, what are we talking about?
I don't want nobody to ever call me bougie.
You hear me.
You see me here steaming my own clothes.
Okay.
Pre-show, steaming my own clothes.
I don't want to hear nobody saying no shit about Amanda Seals is bougie.
You're from Qatar?
Thank you.
Oh, shukran.
Someone said steaming is bougie.
Well, I wasn't going to bring an iron and an ironing board.
But you're not wrong.
Ah, steaming is bougie is funny as hell.
Because after I thought about it, I said, you are correct.
Now, one of these pants has a hole in them.
And I had to just feel the crotch real quick to make sure it wasn't this one.
Because I definitely had forgotten to sew it.
But I do have a sewing kit with me.
Just in case it needed to go down.
So, yeah.
I came on here just to tell y'all that I will be performing my show, What Would the Ancestors Say, at 6 p.m. Eastern.
So, you can get the link in the bio for the live stream and join us.
And, you know, watch it with your kids.
Watch it with your teens.
Watch it with your homegirls.
Your friends.
Everybody.
And, um, watch yourself.
Watch yourself.
I think Angie about to come here with my food.
I think I hear Angie coming in here with my food.
Is that my style?
Me!
So good.
Hey, Angie coming in here with my food.
Bye!